<resources>
    <!--Text and Information taken from https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/ an open encyclopedia-->
    <string name="basil_text">

        Basil (UK: /ˈbæzəl/,[1] US: /ˈbeɪzəl/;[2] Ocimum basilicum), also called great basil or Saint-Joseph\'s-wort, is a culinary herb of the family Lamiaceae (mints).
        \n\nBasil is native to tropical regions from central Africa to Southeast Asia.[3] It is a tender plant, and is used in cuisines worldwide. Depending on the species and cultivar, the leaves may taste somewhat like anise, with a strong, pungent, often sweet smell.
        \n\nThere are many varieties of basil, as well as several related species or hybrids also called basil. The type used commonly as a flavor is typically called sweet basil (or Genovese basil), as opposed to Thai basil (O. basilicum var. thyrsiflora), lemon basil (O. × citriodorum), and holy basil (Ocimum tenuiflorum). While most common varieties of basil are treated as annuals, some are perennial in warm, tropical climates, including holy basil and a cultivar known as "African blue basil".
        \n\nDescription
        \n\nBasil is an annual, or sometimes perennial, herb used for its leaves. Depending on the variety, plants can reach between 30 cm (0.98 ft) and 150 cm (4.9 ft). Its leaves are richly green and ovate, but otherwise come in a wide variety of sizes and shapes depending on cultivar. Leaf sizes range from 3 cm (1.2 in) to 11 cm (4.3 in) long, and between 1 cm (0.39 in) and 6 cm (2.4 in) wide. Basil grows a thick, central taproot. Its flowers are small and white, and grow from a central inflorescence that emerges from the central stem atop the plant.[citation needed]
        \n\nPhytochemistry
        \n\nThe various basils have such different scents because the herb has a number of different essential oils in different proportions for various cultivars.[3] The essential oil from European basil contains high concentrations of linalool and methyl chavicol (estragole), in a ratio of about 3:1.[3][4] Other constituents include: 1,8-cineole, eugenol, and myrcene, among others.[3][5] The clove scent of sweet basil is derived from eugenol.[6] The aroma profile of basil includes 1,8-cineole[7][8] and methyl eugenol.[7][9]
        \n\nDistribution and habitat
        \n\nBasil is native to India and other tropical regions stretching from Africa to Southeast Asia, but has now become globalized due to human cultivation.[3]
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nMost culinary and ornamental basils are cultivars of the species Ocimum basilicum, but other species are also grown and there are many hybrids between species. Traditionally a green plant, some varieties, such as \'Purple Delight\' have leaves that appear purple. Basil grows between 30–130 cm (12–51 in) tall, with opposite, light green, silky leaves 3–11 cm (1.2–4.3 in) long and 1–6 cm (0.39–2.36 in) broad. The flowers are small, white in color and arranged in a terminal spike. Unusual among Lamiaceae, the four stamens and the pistil are not pushed under the upper lip of the corolla, but lie over the inferior lip. After entomophilous pollination, the corolla falls off and four round achenes develop inside the bilabiate calyx.
        \n\nBasil is sensitive to cold, with best growth in hot, dry conditions. It behaves as an annual if there is any chance of a frost. However, due to its popularity, basil is cultivated in many countries around the world. Production areas include countries in the Mediterranean area, those in the temperate zone, and others in subtropical climates.[16]
        \n\nIn Northern Europe, Canada, the northern states of the U.S., and the South Island of New Zealand it will grow best if sown under glass in a peat pot, then planted out in late spring/early summer (when there is little chance of a frost). Additionally, it may be sown in soil once chance of frost is past. It fares best in well-drained, sunny exposure.
        \n\nAlthough basil grows best outdoors, it can be grown indoors in a pot and, like most herbs, will do best on a sun-facing windowsill. It should be kept away from extremely cold drafts, and grows best in strong sunlight, therefore a greenhouse or row cover is ideal if available. It can, however, be grown even in a basement, under fluorescent lights.
        \n\nIf its leaves have wilted from lack of water, it will recover if watered thoroughly and placed in a sunny location. Yellow leaves towards the bottom of the plant are an indication that the plant has been stressed; usually this means that it needs less water, or less or more fertilizer.
        \n\nIn sunnier climates such as Southern Europe, the southern states of the U.S., the North Island of New Zealand, and Australia, basil will thrive when planted outside. It also thrives over the summertime in the central and northern United States, but dies out when temperatures reach freezing point. It will grow back the next year if allowed to go to seed. It will need regular watering, but not as much attention as is needed in other climates.
        \n\nBasil can also be propagated reliably from cuttings with the stems of short cuttings suspended for two weeks or so in water until roots develop.
        \n\nOnce a stem produces flowers, foliage production stops on that stem, the stem becomes woody, and essential oil production declines. To prevent this, a basil-grower may pinch off any flower stems before they are fully mature. Because only the blooming stem is so affected, some stems can be pinched for leaf production, while others are left to bloom for decoration or seeds.
        \n\nOnce the plant is allowed to flower, it may produce seed pods containing small black seeds, which can be saved and planted the following year. Picking the leaves off the plant helps promote growth, largely because the plant responds by converting pairs of leaflets next to the topmost leaves into new stems.
        \n\nBasil is popularly recommended as a companion plant to the tomato. Common claims are that basil may deter pests or improve tomato flavor. However, in double-blind taste tests, basil did not significantly affect the taste of tomatoes when planted adjacent to them.[17][18]
        \n\nDiseases
        \n\nBasil suffers from several plant pathogens that can ruin the crop and reduce yield. Fusarium wilt is a soil-borne fungal disease that will quickly kill younger basil plants. Seedlings may be killed by Pythium damping off. A common foliar disease of basil is gray mold caused by Botrytis cinerea; it can cause infections post-harvest and is capable of killing the entire plant. Black spot can be seen on basil foliage and is caused by the fungi genus Colletotrichum. Downy mildew caused by Peronospora belbahrii is a significant disease, as first reported in Italy in 2004.[19] It was reported in the U.S. in 2007 and 2008.[20][21]
        \n\nNon-pathogenic bacteria found on basil include Novosphingobium species.[22]
        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Basil

    </string>
    <string name="cabbage_text">

        Cabbage or headed cabbage (comprising several cultivars of Brassica oleracea) is a leafy green, red (purple), or white (pale green) biennial plant grown as an annual vegetable crop for its dense-leaved heads. It is descended from the wild cabbage, B. oleracea var. oleracea, and belongs to the \"cole crops\", meaning it is closely related to broccoli and cauliflower (var. botrytis); Brussels sprouts (var. gemmifera); and savoy cabbage (var. sabauda). Brassica rapa is commonly named Chinese, celery or napa cabbage and has many of the same uses. Cabbage is high in nutritional value.
        \n\nCabbage heads generally range from 0.5 to 4 kilograms (1 to 9 lb), and can be green, purple or white. Smooth-leafed, firm-headed green cabbages are the most common. Smooth-leafed purple cabbages and crinkle-leafed savoy cabbages of both colors are rarer. It is a multi-layered vegetable. Under conditions of long sunny days, such as those found at high northern latitudes in summer, cabbages can grow quite large. As of 2012, the heaviest cabbage was 62.71 kilograms (138.25 lb).
        \n\nCabbage was most likely domesticated somewhere in Europe before 1000 BC, although savoys were not developed until the 16th century AD. By the Middle Ages, cabbage had become a prominent part of European cuisine. Cabbage heads are generally picked during the first year of the plant\'s life cycle, but plants intended for seed are allowed to grow a second year and must be kept separate from other cole crops to prevent cross-pollination. Cabbage is prone to several nutrient deficiencies, as well as to multiple pests, and bacterial and fungal diseases.
        \n\nCabbages are prepared many different ways for eating; they can be pickled, fermented (for dishes such as sauerkraut), steamed, stewed, sautéed, braised, or eaten raw. Cabbage is a good source of vitamin K, vitamin C and dietary fiber. The Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (FAO) reported that world production of cabbage and other brassicas for 2014 was 71.8 million metric tonnes, with China accounting for 47% of the world total.
        \n\nDescription
        \n\nCabbage seedlings have a thin taproot and cordate (heart-shaped) cotyledon. The first leaves produced are ovate (egg-shaped) with a lobed petiole. Plants are 40–60 cm (16–24 in) tall in their first year at the mature vegetative stage, and 1.5–2.0 m (4.9–6.6 ft) tall when flowering in the second year.[14] Heads average between 0.5 and 4 kg (1 and 8 lb), with fast-growing, earlier-maturing varieties producing smaller heads.[15] Most cabbages have thick, alternating leaves, with margins that range from wavy or lobed to highly dissected; some varieties have a waxy bloom on the leaves. Plants have root systems that are fibrous and shallow.[10] About 90 percent of the root mass is in the upper 20–30 cm (8–12 in) of soil; some lateral roots can penetrate up to 2 m (6.6 ft) deep.[14]
        \n\nThe inflorescence is an unbranched and indeterminate terminal raceme measuring 50–100 cm (20–40 in) tall,[14] with flowers that are yellow or white. Each flower has four petals set in a perpendicular pattern, as well as four sepals, six stamens, and a superior ovary that is two-celled and contains a single stigma and style. Two of the six stamens have shorter filaments. The fruit is a silique that opens at maturity through dehiscence to reveal brown or black seeds that are small and round in shape. Self-pollination is impossible, and plants are cross-pollinated by insects.[10] The initial leaves form a rosette shape comprising 7 to 15 leaves, each measuring 25–35 cm (10–14 in) by 20–30 cm (8–12 in);[14] after this, leaves with shorter petioles develop and heads form through the leaves cupping inward.[2]
        \n\nMany shapes, colors and leaf textures are found in various cultivated varieties of cabbage. Leaf types are generally divided between crinkled-leaf, loose-head savoys and smooth-leaf firm-head cabbages, while the color spectrum includes white and a range of greens and purples. Oblate, round and pointed shapes are found.[16]
        \n\nCabbage has been selectively bred for head weight and morphological characteristics, frost hardiness, fast growth and storage ability. The appearance of the cabbage head has been given importance in selective breeding, with varieties being chosen for shape, color, firmness and other physical characteristics.[17] Breeding objectives are now focused on increasing resistance to various insects and diseases and improving the nutritional content of cabbage.[18] Scientific research into the genetic modification of B. oleracea crops, including cabbage, has included European Union and United States explorations of greater insect and herbicide resistance.[19]
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nCabbage is generally grown for its densely leaved heads, produced during the first year of its biennial cycle. Plants perform best when grown in well-drained soil in a location that receives full sun. Different varieties prefer different soil types, ranging from lighter sand to heavier clay, but all prefer fertile ground with a pH between 6.0 and 6.8.[55] For optimal growth, there must be adequate levels of nitrogen in the soil, especially during the early head formation stage, and sufficient phosphorus and potassium during the early stages of expansion of the outer leaves.[56] Temperatures between 4 and 24 °C (39 and 75 °F) prompt the best growth, and extended periods of higher or lower temperatures may result in premature bolting (flowering).[55] Flowering induced by periods of low temperatures (a process called vernalization) only occurs if the plant is past the juvenile period. The transition from a juvenile to adult state happens when the stem diameter is about 6 mm (0.24 in). Vernalization allows the plant to grow to an adequate size before flowering. In certain climates, cabbage can be planted at the beginning of the cold period and survive until a later warm period without being induced to flower, a practice that was common in the eastern US.[57]
        \n\nPlants are generally started in protected locations early in the growing season before being transplanted outside, although some are seeded directly into the ground from which they will be harvested.[15] Seedlings typically emerge in about 4–6 days from seeds planted 1.3 cm (0.5 in) deep at a soil temperature between 20 and 30 °C (68 and 86 °F).[58] Growers normally place plants 30 to 61 cm (12 to 24 in) apart.[15] Closer spacing reduces the resources available to each plant (especially the amount of light) and increases the time taken to reach maturity.[59] Some varieties of cabbage have been developed for ornamental use; these are generally called "flowering cabbage". They do not produce heads and feature purple or green outer leaves surrounding an inner grouping of smaller leaves in white, red, or pink.[15] Early varieties of cabbage take about 70 days from planting to reach maturity, while late varieties take about 120 days.[60] Cabbages are mature when they are firm and solid to the touch. They are harvested by cutting the stalk just below the bottom leaves with a blade. The outer leaves are trimmed, and any diseased, damaged, or necrotic leaves are removed.[61] Delays in harvest can result in the head splitting as a result of expansion of the inner leaves and continued stem growth.[62] Factors that contribute to reduced head weight include: growth in the compacted soils that result from no-till farming practices, drought, waterlogging, insect and disease incidence, and shading and nutrient stress caused by weeds.[56]
        \n\nWhen being grown for seed, cabbages must be isolated from other B. oleracea subspecies, including the wild varieties, by 0.8 to 1.6 km (0.5 to 1 mi) to prevent cross-pollination. Other Brassica species, such as B. rapa, B. juncea, B. nigra, B. napus and Raphanus sativus, do not readily cross-pollinate.[63]
        \n\nCultivars
        \n\nThere are several cultivar groups of cabbage, each including many cultivars:
        \n\n\tSavoy – Characterized by crimped or curly leaves, mild flavor and tender texture[21]
        \n\n\tSpring Greens – Loose-headed, commonly sliced and steamed[21]
        \n\n\tGreen – Light to dark green, slightly pointed heads.[21] This is the most commonly grown cultivar.[15]
        \n\n\tRed – Smooth red leaves, often used for pickling or stewing[21]
        \n\n\tWhite, also called Dutch – Smooth, pale green leaves[21]
        \n\nSome sources only delineate three cultivars: savoy, red and white, with spring greens and green cabbage being subsumed into the latter.[64]
        \n\nCultivation problems
        \n\nSee also: List of Lepidoptera that feed on Brassica
        \n\nDue to its high level of nutrient requirements, cabbage is prone to nutrient deficiencies, including boron, calcium, phosphorus and potassium.[55] There are several physiological disorders that can affect the postharvest appearance of cabbage. Internal tip burn occurs when the margins of inside leaves turn brown, but the outer leaves look normal. Necrotic spot is where there are oval sunken spots a few millimeters across that are often grouped around the midrib. In pepper spot, tiny black spots occur on the areas between the veins, which can increase during storage.[65]
        \n\nFungal diseases include wirestem, which causes weak or dying transplants; Fusarium yellows, which result in stunted and twisted plants with yellow leaves; and blackleg (see Leptosphaeria maculans), which leads to sunken areas on stems and gray-brown spotted leaves.[66] The fungi Alternaria brassicae and A. brassicicola cause dark leaf spots in affected plants. They are both seedborne and airborne, and typically propagate from spores in infected plant debris left on the soil surface for up to twelve weeks after harvest. Rhizoctonia solani causes the post-emergence disease wirestem, resulting in killed seedlings ("damping-off"), root rot or stunted growth and smaller heads.[67]
        \n\nOne of the most common bacterial diseases to affect cabbage is black rot, caused by Xanthomonas campestris, which causes chlorotic and necrotic lesions that start at the leaf margins, and wilting of plants. Clubroot, caused by the soilborne slime mold-like organism Plasmodiophora brassicae, results in swollen, club-like roots. Downy mildew, a parasitic disease caused by the oomycete Peronospora parasitica,[67] produces pale leaves with white, brownish or olive mildew on the lower leaf surfaces; this is often confused with the fungal disease powdery mildew.[66]
        \n\nPests include root-knot nematodes and cabbage maggots, which produce stunted and wilted plants with yellow leaves; aphids, which induce stunted plants with curled and yellow leaves; harlequin bugs, which cause white and yellow leaves; thrips, which lead to leaves with white-bronze spots; striped flea beetles, which riddle leaves with small holes; and caterpillars, which leave behind large, ragged holes in leaves.[66] The caterpillar stage of the "small cabbage white butterfly" (Pieris rapae), commonly known in the United States as the "imported cabbage worm", is a major cabbage pest in most countries. The large white butterfly (Pieris brassicae) is prevalent in eastern European countries. The diamondback moth (Plutella xylostella) and the cabbage moth (Mamestra brassicae) thrive in the higher summer temperatures of continental Europe, where they cause considerable damage to cabbage crops.[68] The cabbage looper (Trichoplusia ni) is infamous in North America for its voracious appetite and for producing frass that contaminates plants.[69] In India, the diamondback moth has caused losses up to 90 percent in crops that were not treated with insecticide.[70] Destructive soil insects include the cabbage root fly (Delia radicum) and the cabbage maggot (Hylemya brassicae), whose larvae can burrow into the part of plant consumed by humans.[68]
        \n\nPlanting near other members of the cabbage family, or where these plants have been placed in previous years, can prompt the spread of pests and disease.[55] Excessive water and excessive heat can also cause cultivation problems.[66]
        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cabbage

    </string>
    <string name="spearmint_text">

        Spearmint, also known as garden mint, common mint, lamb mint and mackerel mint,[5][6] is a species of mint, Mentha spicata, native to Europe and southern temperate Asia, extending from Ireland in the west to southern China in the east. It is naturalized in many other temperate parts of the world, including northern and southern Africa, North America and South America.[7][8] It is used as a flavoring in food and herbal teas. The aromatic oil, called oil of spearmint, is also used as a flavoring and sometimes as a scent.
        \n\nThe species and its subspecies have many synonyms, including Mentha crispa, Mentha crispata and Mentha viridis.
        \n\nDescription
        \n\nSpearmint is a perennial herbaceous plant. It is 30–100 cm (12–39 in) tall, with variably hairless to hairy stems and foliage, and a wide-spreading fleshy underground rhizome from which it grows. The leaves are 5–9 cm (2–3 1⁄2 in) long and 1.5–3 cm (1⁄2–1 1⁄4 in) broad, with a serrated margin. The stem is square-shaped, a trademark of the mint family of herbs. Spearmint produces flowers in slender spikes, each flower pink or white in colour, 2.5–3 mm (0.098–0.118 in) long, and broad.[8][9] Spearmint flowers in the summer (from July to September in the northern hemisphere),[10] and has relatively large seeds, which measure 0.62–0.90 mm (0.024–0.035 in).[10] The name \'spear\' mint derives from the pointed leaf tips.[11]
        \n\nMentha spicata varies considerably in leaf blade dimensions, the prominence of leaf veins, and pubescence.[12]
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nSpearmint grows well in nearly all temperate climates. Gardeners often grow it in pots or planters due to its invasive, spreading rhizomes.
        \n\nSpearmint leaves can be used fresh, dried, or frozen. They can also be preserved in salt, sugar, sugar syrup, alcohol, or oil. The leaves lose their aromatic appeal after the plant flowers. It can be dried by cutting just before, or right (at peak) as the flowers open, about one-half to three-quarters the way down the stalk (leaving smaller shoots room to grow). Some dispute exists as to what drying method works best; some prefer different materials (such as plastic or cloth) and different lighting conditions (such as darkness or sunlight).
        \n\nMedical research
        \n\nAntitumor
        \n\nThe main chemical component of spearmint is the terpenoid carvone,[26][27] which has been shown to aid in the inhibition of tumors.[28] Perillyl alcohol, an additional terpenoid found in lower concentrations in spearmint, positively effects the regulation of various cell substances involved in cell growth and differentiation.[29][28]
        \n\nAntioxidant
        \n\nStudies on spearmint have shown varying results on the antioxidant effects of the plant and its extracts.[27][30][31] Results have ranged from spearmint essential oil displaying considerable free radical scavenging activity[27] to no antioxidant activity in spearmint essential oil, but strong activity in spearmint methanolic extract.[30] Antioxidant activity has been shown to be significantly higher in spearmint that is dried at lower temperatures rather than high.[31][32] It is suggested this is due to the degradation of phenolics at high temperatures.[31] In experiments demonstrating antioxidant properties in spearmint oil, the major component, carvone, alone showed lower antioxidant activity.
        \n\nAntimicrobial
        \n\nSpearmint has been historically used for its antimicrobial activity, which is likely due to the high concentration of carvone.[27][30] Its in vitro antibacterial activity has been compared to, and is even said to surpass, that of amoxicillin, penicillin, and streptomycin.[27][33] Spearmint oil is found to have higher activity against Gram-positive bacteria compared to Gram-negative bacteria,[27] which may be due to differing sensitivities to oils.[34][35] The degree of antimicrobial activity varies with the type of microorganism tested.[27]
        \n\nAdditional properties
        \n\nStudies have found significant antiandrogen effects in spearmint, specifically following routine spearmint herbal tea ingestion.[36][37] Antispasmodic effects have been displayed in spearmint oil and carvone, the main chemical component of spearmint.[38]
        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spearmint

    </string>
    <string name="dill_text">

        Dill (Anethum graveolens) is an annual herb in the celery family Apiaceae. It is the only species in the genus Anethum. Dill is grown widely in Eurasia where its leaves and seeds are used as a herb or spice for flavouring food.
        \n\nGrowth
        \n\nDill grows up to 40–60 cm (16–24 in), with slender hollow stems and alternate, finely divided, softly delicate leaves 10–20 cm (4–8 in) long. The ultimate leaf divisions are 1–2 mm (0.04–0.08 in) broad, slightly broader than the similar leaves of fennel, which are threadlike, less than 1 mm (0.04 in) broad, but harder in texture. The flowers are white to yellow, in small umbels 2–9 cm (0.8–3.5 in) diameter. The seeds are 4–5 mm (0.16–0.20 in) long and 1 mm (0.04 in) thick, and straight to slightly curved with a longitudinally ridged surface.
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nSuccessful cultivation requires warm to hot summers with high sunshine levels; even partial shade will reduce the yield substantially.[citation needed] It also prefers rich, well-drained soil. The seeds are viable for three to ten years.[citation needed] The plants are somewhat monocarpic and quickly die after "bolting" (producing seeds). Hot temperatures may quicken bolting.[citation needed]
        \n\nThe seed is harvested by cutting the flower heads off the stalks when the seed is beginning to ripen. The seed heads are placed upside down in a paper bag and left in a warm, dry place for a week. The seeds then separate from the stems easily for storage in an airtight container.
        \n\nThese plants, like their fennel and parsley relatives, often are eaten by Black swallowtail caterpillars in areas where that species occurs.[13] For this reason, they may be included in some butterfly gardens.
        \n\nCompanion planting
        \n\nWhen used as a companion plant, dill attracts many beneficial insects as the umbrella flower heads go to seed. It makes a good companion plant for cucumbers and broccoli.
        \n\nIt is a poor companion plant for carrots and tomatoes.[14]
        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dill

    </string>
    <string name="parsley_text">

        \n\nParsley or garden parsley (Petroselinum crispum) is a species of flowering plant in the family Apiaceae that is native to the central Mediterranean region (Cyprus, southern Italy, Greece, Portugal, Spain, Malta, Morocco, Algeria, and Tunisia), but has naturalized elsewhere in Europe, and is widely cultivated as a herb, a spice, and a vegetable.
        \n\nWhere it grows as a biennial, in the first year, it forms a rosette of tripinnate leaves, 10–25 cm (3.9–9.8 in) long, with numerous 1–3 cm (0.4–1.2 in) leaflets and a taproot used as a food store over the winter. In the second year, it grows a flowering stem with sparser leaves and umbels with yellow to yellowish-green flowers.
        \n\nParsley is widely used in European, Middle Eastern, and American cuisine. Curly leaf parsley is often used as a garnish. In central Europe, eastern Europe, and southern Europe, as well as in western Asia, many dishes are served with fresh green chopped parsley sprinkled on top. Flat leaf parsley is similar, but it is easier to cultivate, and some say it has a stronger flavor. Root parsley is very common in central, eastern, and southern European cuisines, where it is used as a snack or a vegetable in many soups, stews, and casseroles.
        \n\nNutritional content
        \n\nParsley is a source of flavonoids and antioxidants, especially luteolin, apigenin,[10] folic acid, vitamin K, vitamin C, and vitamin A. Half a tablespoon (a gram) of dried parsley contains about 6.0 µg of lycopene and 10.7 µg of alpha carotene as well as 82.9 µg of lutein+zeaxanthin and 80.7 µg of beta carotene.[11]
        \n\nPrecautions
        \n\nExcessive consumption of parsley should be avoided by pregnant women. Normal food quantities are safe for pregnant women, but consuming excessively large amounts may have uterotonic effects.[12]
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nParsley grows best in moist, well-drained soil, with full sun. It grows best between 22–30 °C (72–86 °F), and usually is grown from seed.[9] Germination is slow, taking four to six weeks,[9] and it often is difficult because of furanocoumarins in its seed coat.[13] Typically, plants grown for the leaf crop are spaced 10 cm apart, while those grown as a root crop are spaced 20 cm apart to allow for the root development.[9]
        \n\nParsley attracts several species of wildlife. Some swallowtail butterflies use parsley as a host plant for their larvae; their caterpillars are black and green striped with yellow dots, and will feed on parsley for two weeks before turning into butterflies. Bees and other nectar-feeding insects also visit the flowers. Birds such as the goldfinch feed on the seeds.
        \n\nCultivars
        \n\nIn cultivation, parsley is subdivided into several cultivar groups,[14] depending on the form of the plant, which is related to its end use. Often these are treated as botanical varieties,[15] but they are cultivated selections, not of natural botanical origin.[8]
        \n\nThe two main groups of parsley used as herbs are French, or curly leaf (P. crispum crispum group; syn. P. crispum var. crispum); and, Italian, or flat leaf (P. crispum neapolitanum group; syn. P. crispum var. neapolitanum). Of these, the neapolitanum group more closely resembles the natural wild species.[citation needed] Flat-leaved parsley is preferred by some gardeners as it is easier to cultivate, being more tolerant of both rain and sunshine,[16] and is said to have a stronger flavor[9] — although this is disputed[16] — while curly leaf parsley is preferred by others because of its more decorative appearance in garnishing.[16][17] A third type, sometimes grown in southern Italy, has thick leaf stems resembling celery.[16]
        \n\nAnother type of parsley is grown as a root vegetable, the Hamburg root parsley (P. crispum radicosum group, syn. P. crispum var. tuberosum). This type of parsley produces much thicker roots than types cultivated for their leaves. Although seldom used in Britain and the United States, root parsley is common in central and eastern European cuisine, where it is used in soups and stews, or simply eaten raw, as a snack (similar to carrots).[16]
        \n\nAlthough root parsley looks similar to the parsnip, which is among its closest relatives in the family Apiaceae, its taste is quite different.
        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Parsley

    </string>
    <string name="thyme_text">

        Thyme (/taɪm/) is any member of the genus Thymus of aromatic perennial evergreen herbs in the mint family Lamiaceae. Thymes are relatives of the oregano genus Origanum. They have culinary, medicinal, and ornamental uses, the species most commonly cultivated and used for culinary purposes being Thymus vulgaris.
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nThyme is best cultivated in a hot, sunny location with well-drained soil. It is generally planted in the spring, and thereafter grows as a perennial. It can be propagated by seed, cuttings, or dividing rooted sections of the plant. It tolerates drought well.[6] The plants can take deep freezes and are found growing wild on mountain highlands.
        \n\nAntimicrobial properties
        \n\nOil of thyme, the essential oil of common thyme (Thymus vulgaris), contains 20–54% thymol.[8] Thyme essential oil also contains a range of additional compounds, such as p-cymene, myrcene, borneol, and linalool.[9] Thymol, an antiseptic, is an active ingredient in various commercially produced mouthwashes such as Listerine.[10] Before the advent of modern antibiotics, oil of thyme was used to medicate bandages.[2]
        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thyme

    </string>
    <string name="chives_text">

        Chives, scientific name Allium schoenoprasum, are an edible species of the genus Allium.[3] Their close relatives include the garlic, shallot, leek, scallion,[4] and Chinese onion.[5]A perennial plant, it is widespread in nature across much of Europe, Asia, and North America.[6][7][8][9][10][11]
        \n\nA. schoenoprasum is the only species of Allium native to both the New and the Old Worlds.[12][13]
        \n\nChives are a commonly used herb and can be found in grocery stores or grown in home gardens. In culinary use, the scapes and the unopened, immature flower buds are diced and used as an ingredient for fish, potatoes, soups, and other dishes. The edible flowers can be used in salads.[14] Chives have insect-repelling properties that can be used in gardens to control pests.[15]
        \n\nThe plant provides a great deal of nectar for pollinators. It was rated in the top 10 for most nectar production (nectar per unit cover per year) in a UK plants survey conducted by the AgriLand project which is supported by the UK Insect Pollinators Initiative.[16]
        \n\nDescription
        \n\nChives are a bulb-forming herbaceous perennial plant, growing to 30–50 cm (12–20 in) tall. The bulbs are slender, conical, 2–3 cm (3⁄4–1 1⁄4 in) long and 1 cm (1⁄2 in) broad, and grow in dense clusters from the roots. The scapes (or stems) are hollow and tubular, up to 50 cm (20 in) long and 2–3 mm (1⁄16–1⁄8 in) across, with a soft texture, although, prior to the emergence of a flower, they may appear stiffer than usual. The grass-like[14] leaves, which are shorter than the scapes, are also hollow and tubular, or terete, (round in cross-section) which distinguishes it at a glance from garlic chives (Allium tuberosum). The flowers are pale purple, and star-shaped with six petals, 1–2 cm (1⁄2–3⁄4 in) wide, and produced in a dense inflorescence of 10-30 together; before opening, the inflorescence is surrounded by a papery bract. The seeds are produced in a small, three-valved capsule, maturing in summer. The herb flowers from April to May in the southern parts of its habitat zones and in June in the northern parts.[17][18]
        \n\nChives are the only species of Allium native to both the New and the Old Worlds. Sometimes, the plants found in North America are classified as A. schoenoprasum var. sibiricum, although this is disputed. Differences between specimens are significant. One example was found in northern Maine growing solitary, instead of in clumps, also exhibiting dingy grey flowers.[19]
        \n\nAlthough chives are repulsive to insects in general, due to their sulfur compounds, their flowers attract bees, and they are at times kept to increase desired insect life.[20]
        \n\nCultivation
        \n\nChives are cultivated both for their culinary uses and their ornamental value; the violet flowers are often used in ornamental dry bouquets.[36] The flowers are also edible and are used in salads,[37] or used to make Blossom vinegars.[38]
        \n\nChives thrive in well-drained soil, rich in organic matter, with a pH of 6-7 and full sun.[11] They can be grown from seed and mature in summer, or early the following spring. Typically, chives need to be germinated at a temperature of 15 to 20 °C (60-70 °F) and kept moist. They can also be planted under a cloche or germinated indoors in cooler climates, then planted out later. After at least four weeks, the young shoots should be ready to be planted out. They are also easily propagated by division.[39]
        \n\nIn cold regions, chives die back to the underground bulbs in winter, with the new leaves appearing in early spring. Chives starting to look old can be cut back to about 2–5 cm. When harvesting, the needed number of stalks should be cut to the base.[39] During the growing season, the plant continually regrows leaves, allowing for a continuous harvest.[39]
        \n\nChives are susceptible to damage by leek moth larvae, which bore into the leaves or bulbs of the plant.[40]

        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chives

    </string>
    <string name="_text">



        \n\nLink to original webpage: \nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thyme

    </string>

</resources>
